Okay, so now we can start the Roger Ebert review word cloud.
لا بأس، إذًا يمكننا الآن البدء في مراجعة روجر إيبرت لكلمة سحاب.
So the first thing you need,
إذًا أول شيء نحتاجه
the text from each of his reviews,
هو النص من كلٍ من مراجعاته
for each of the movies on the Rotten Tomatoes Top 100 Movies of All Time list.
لكلٍ من الأفلام الموجودة على قائمة موقع Rotten Tomatoes لأفضل 100 فيلم على مر الزمن.
They live on his website.
توجد هذه الأفلام على موقعه الإليكتروني.
Lucky for you I've pre-gathered all of this text in the form of 100.txt files.
لحسن حظكم أنني قد جمعتُ مسبقًا كل هذا النص في شكل ملفات 100.txt،
I put them on this Udacity hosted web page
ووضعتُها على صفحة الويب هذه التي تستضيفها Udacity،
and you're going to download them all programmatically.
وسوف تنزِّلونها جميعًا بشكل مبرمج.
Yes, you can point and click and download each file manually but that would take forever,
نعم، يمكنكم الإشارة إلى كل ملف والنقر فوقه وتنزيله يدويًا، لكن هذا سيستغرق الوقت إلى الأبد
especially if someone else wants to reproduce your analysis.
لا سيما إذا أراد آخرون إعادة إنتاج تحليلاتكم.
If they want to check your work, for example,
إذا أراد هؤلاء الآخرون مراجعة عملكم مثلًا،
they can download all of the files with the execution of a few lines of code.
فيمكنهم تنزيل جميع الملفات مع تنفيذ بعضة سطور من الكود.
So downloading files from Internet programmatically
إذًا تنزيل الملفات من شبكة الإنترنت بشكل مبرمج
is best for scalability and reproducibility.
هو الأفضل لتحقيق قابلية للتطوير والنسخ.
In practice you really only need to know one thing
لن تحتاجوا حقًا في الممارسة سوى معرفة شيء واحد
to download files like this, Python's request library.
كي تنزِّلوا ملفات كهذه، وهو مكتبة طلب Python.
Knowing a bit of HTTP aka
معرفة القليل حول HTTP، وهو اختصار
Hypertext Transfer Protocol will help you understand what's going on under the hood here.
Hypertext Transfer Protocol (بروتوكول نقل النص التشعبي) ستساعدكم في فهم ما يجري بشكل كامن هنا.
So next you'll learn the basics of HTTP along with Python's request library.
لذا ستتعلمون فيما يلي أساسيات HTTP، إلى جانب مكتبة طلب Python.